Hello friends welcome to another video of
stock market friends III Lord's has
presented its September quarter financial results, the unaudited results are
out for the quarter end and
financial year ended which is for the quarter
end and half year ended and along with that
an ultimate dividend of 5.5 per equity share has also been
declared and paid
whose record date has been fixed for 28th
August 2024 so now we move on to the
company's results and guys the
numbers given here are in lakhs if we
talk about income then this time the income is
58.6 crores, in June'24 the income is
533519 crores and in September'23 the
income is 50.3 crores, the income has been seen
increasing in both quarter on quarter and year on year the
expense of the company has been
5186 4 crores, in June'24 it was 48.4 crores
and in September'23 it was 4453 crores  There was an expense, the
company's expenses have also increased
according to the income, but here the
underwriting profit, there has actually been a
loss, there was an underwriting loss of Rs
16.9 crore, in June 24 there was an underwriting profit loss of Rs 346.6 crore
and in September 23 there was an
underwriting profit loss of Rs 147 crore, this time the
loss has been recovered, the year has
increased the loss and transferred Rs
664 crore to the profit and loss account,
after which the total expense of the company was incurred,
after that if seen, there is an expense of Rs 20.6 crore,
in the last quarter there was an
addition of Rs 19.5 crore and in September 23 there was a
de-charge of Rs 55.3 crore, after which the
profit of the company came out to be Rs 919 crore,
in June 24 there was a profit of Rs
7739 crore and in September 23 there
is a profit of Rs 6763 crore, quarter on quarter
year on year the operating profit
of the company has increased after tax  The profit is of
6939 crores, in June 24 it was
58.3 crores, in September 23 it is 577 crores,
quarter on quarter year on
year it has been seen increasing,
EPS
of 14.05 has been seen increasing in both quarter on quarter and year on year
and if we look at Guys company then Guys has
presented very strong results because
both income and profit are
seen increasing, whether it is quarter on
quarter or year on year, profit and income are
seen increasing,
if we talk about its shares, the
result has come around 5 PM
and if we talk about the shares, the
share has closed at ₹1, it has crashed by 1.4 today, there is a loss of
3.3 in five days, there is a
loss of 6 in one month, Guys company is seeing a
huge loss, downfall is being seen,
Dow trend is being seen but now there are
chances that the company's share can reverse from here
because the result company  It
is a very strong page, so if you
want to invest in it, you can do it.
If you are in loss, you can average it,
but still, before taking any decision, do
consult your advisor. So,
we end the video here.
If you have any doubt, ask in the comment box. We will meet
in the next video. Till then, bye bye.